Guide to the Stanford University, School of Humanities and Sciences, Individually Designed Majors Honors Theses
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, School of Humanities and Sciences, Individually Designed Majors honors theses
1988-2002
SC4-4999
Stanford University. School of Humanities and Sciences.
0.5 Linear feet (15 volumes in 1 box)
Honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University School of Humanities and Sciences Individually Designed Major Program.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Theses were transferred to the Stanford University Archives from the Hume Writing Center in 2011.
Information about Access
The collection is open for research use; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. No photocopies may be made.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University School of Humanities and Sciences Individually Designed Major Program.
Access Terms
Student papers.
Collection Contents
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2011-152
  - Ben-Amos, Ilana, Seeing the savage: photographing Papua New Guineans and Samoans., 1993 (Box 1)
  - Kasson, Peter M., Rates of peptide association to the class II MHC molecule I-Ek., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Greene, Jacob, Japan's emerging online banking industry., 2002 (Box 1)
  - Welland, Sasha Su-Ling, Mirror of the past: reflections on a Chinese family history., 1991 (Box 1)
  - Burdick, Robert Alan, Illustration as demonstration: the nature of experience in the Vesalian illustrations., 1988 (Box 1)
  - Gandhi, Sunil P., Neuronal correlates of spatial attention in human primary visual cortex., 1998 (Box 1)
  - Ferguson, Patty, Negotiating the labyrinth of federal recognition: a California case study., 1997 (Box 1)
  - Simmons, D'Neisha, Visual discrimination: appearance-related issues that Black women face in corporate organizations., undated [1999] (Box 1)
  - Dittman, Jeremy, Molecular and physiological characterization of Shaker potassium channel gating., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Pang, Karen, Culture and body image: a study of Asian American women., 1994 (Box 1)
  - Liu, Michelle, The phenomenon of Chinese diaspora in Paris., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Ho, Cathi, A study of residential architecture at Stanford University Manzanita Park Phase III: program report., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Alvarez, Nancy E., Sex and power in a textual variant of the Collectio Tripartita: reconstructing an ideology of reform identity from a Canon Law collection at the Benedictine Monastery of Admont, c.1100-1125., 2001 (Box 1)
  - Manzari, Johnnie, Designing a digital photograph viewing system for the American family., 2001 (Box 1)
  - Powell, Laura Solliday, Ecotourism as a strategy of sustainable development., 1991
  - Kahn, Jonathan, The Political Economy of Thorstein Veblen and John Kenneth Galbraith, 1974; 1 folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Osborne, David, An American Tragedy: Rexford Guy Tugwell and the Contradictions of Liberal Reformism, 1974; 1 folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 2)